time flies
시간은 흐른다
Do you like this place?
여기 괜찮 니?
Yes
예
again
다시
next time
다음번
Let's meet our friends
친구들을 만나자
OK
좋아요
we have been together for a long time
우리는 오랫동안 함께 있었어요
we have never met your friends before
우리는 전에 네 친구를 만난 적이 없어
We'll see you when we get back
돌아가면 뵙겠습니다
do not be afraid
두려워 하지마
What did you eat?
무엇을 먹었나요?
chocolate
초콜릿
let's go
갑시다
Many auction participants
경매 참가자 다수
They have submitted the auction documents
그들은 경매 서류를 제출했습니다
Chinese content
중국어 콘텐츠
different
다른
we got
우리는 얻었다
Mr. Zhang didn’t understand
장 씨는 이해하지 못했습니다
Real card
실물카드
we counted
우리는 세었다
Mr. Zhang’s situation
장 씨의 상황
in danger
위험에
Yaoyao is not sure yet?
Yaoyao는 아직 확실하지 않나요?
she said she needed some time
그녀는 시간이 좀 필요하다고 했어
we don't have time
우리에겐 시간이 없어
Let’s start Plan B right away
당장 플랜 B를 시작하자
Go to Tianhai
텐하이로 가세요
Instantly
곧
OK
좋아요
they are back
그들은 돌아왔다
On Tianhai Expressway
텐하이 고속도로에서
10 kilometers left
10km 남았습니다
ten kilometers
10킬로미터
OK
좋아요
We set up a switch in the cost terminal
비용 터미널에 스위치를 설치했습니다.
As soon as someone appears
누군가 나타나자마자
We will arrest him immediately
우리는 그를 즉시 체포할 것입니다
OK
좋아요
It's beautiful outside
밖은 아름다워
your man
네 남자
he is no longer trustworthy
그 사람은 더 이상 믿을 수 없어
I still have a chance for revenge
아직 복수할 기회는 있어
i think you have the ability
내 생각엔 너한테 능력이 있는 것 같아
But you should give up cutting off your arms
하지만 팔 자르는 건 포기해야 해
This way you can continue your mission
이렇게 하면 임무를 계속할 수 있습니다.
I will deal with him
나는 그 사람을 처리할 것이다
he is your partner
그는 당신의 파트너입니다
He knows the organization
그는 그 조직을 알고 있다
Located in Tianhai
톈하이에 위치
If it falls into the hands of Guoan
만약 궈안의 손에 넘어간다면
Not very good
아주 좋은하지
To serve you and order
당신을 섬기고 주문하기 위해
Understood
이해했다
Don't worry
괜찮아요
Your new partner is much better than him
당신의 새로운 파트너는 그 사람보다 훨씬 낫습니다
Have you started plan B?
플랜 B를 시작하셨나요?
Yes
예
Now Guoan
나우궈안
it is close to the foundation of the organization
조직의 기초에 가깝다
if we don't
우리가 그렇지 않으면
I'm afraid it's too late
너무 늦었나 봐
I sent Tony to deal with her.
나는 그녀를 처리하기 위해 Tony를 보냈습니다.
Priority now
지금 우선순위
you have to take off your tail
꼬리를 떼어내야 해
be safe
안전한
Understood
이해했다
I've prepared something for you
내가 당신을 위해 뭔가를 준비했어요
It seems like this period
이 시기인 것 같아요
You two get along very well
둘이 아주 잘 지내요
Fully comply with organizational requirements
조직의 요구 사항을 완벽하게 준수
Pack everything up here as soon as possible
가능한 한 빨리 여기에 모든 것을 포장하세요.
Let’s go to Tianhai
텐하이로 가자
It's time to adapt
이제 적응할 시간이다
your new identity
당신의 새로운 정체성
Things that shouldn't be missed
놓치지 말아야 할 것들
as soon as possible
최대한 빨리
I lived a happy life during this time
그동안 행복한 삶을 살았습니다
be my happy wife
나의 행복한 아내가 되어주세요
my partner is still happy
내 파트너는 여전히 행복해
all is well
다 괜찮아
but this is temporary
하지만 이건 일시적이야
Maybe marriage will come back one day
언젠가는 결혼이 다시 돌아올지도 모르지
But that person
그런데 그 사람
Not necessarily you
반드시 당신은 아닙니다
Then it gets weird
그러면 이상해진다
as a neighbor
이웃으로서
Are you weird?
당신은 이상한가요?
Looks good
좋아 보인다
keep the ring
반지를 지켜라
It's better to sell it for money
돈주고 파는게 나을듯
worthless
가치 없는
accept
수용하다
say
말하다
The main card you get
기본으로 받는 카드
Forged
서서히 나아가는
are you sure
확실합니까
The Office of National Security may step in
국가안보실이 개입할 수도 있다.
What time will we arrive?
우리는 몇시에 도착할까요?
Understood
이해했다
I'm on my way back
난 돌아오는 중이야
Are you calling me?
나한테 전화하는 거야?
you are being watched
당신은 감시되고 있습니다
Looking for a way to escape
탈출할 방법을 찾고 있어요
OK
좋아요
what happened?
무슨 일이에요?
there is nothing
아무것도 없다
this is not a way out
이건 탈출구가 아니야
Tianyang
텐양
The target has exited the highway early
대상이 고속도로를 일찍 빠져나왔습니다.
no attention
관심 없음
The way back to Tianhai
텐하이로 돌아가는 길
can he
그가 할수 있나요
Leo follows
레오가 팔로우한다
they were discovered
그들은 발견되었다
impossible
불가능한
Our process
우리의 프로세스
always been hidden
항상 숨겨져 있었어
Leo.
사자 별자리.
Look at him. Follow him.
그를 봐. 그를 따라가세요.
watch your movements
움직임을 조심해
we'll go right away
우리 바로 갈게
you
너
what happened?
무슨 일이에요?
there is nothing
아무것도 없다
Why are you driving so fast?
왜 그렇게 빨리 운전해요?
target stop
목표 정지
Location synced
위치가 동기화되었습니다.
in your car
당신의 차에
I'll go there now
지금 거기로 갈게
Chu Yan
초염
I have some questions now
지금 몇 가지 질문이 있습니다.
Help me drive to Tianhai
텐하이까지 운전하는 것을 도와주세요
Can you drive a manual guardrail?
수동 가드레일을 운전할 수 있나요?
I don't know how to drive
나는 운전하는 방법을 모른다
Why do you have a gun?
왜 총을 갖고 있나요?
Who are you?
누구세요?
What’s wrong with you?
무슨 문제 있어?
silent
조용한
I can't now
지금은 할 수 없어
I have to explain a lot to you
너에게 많은 것을 설명해야 해
Let's break up here
여기서 헤어지자
What does separation mean?
이별은 무슨 뜻인가요?
I don't like girls who talk a lot
나는 말 많은 여자를 좋아하지 않는다
i know your parents
난 네 부모님을 알아
He lives at No. 23 Nanyuan
그는 난위안 23번지에 산다.
I don't want to treat you like this
난 당신을 이렇게 대하고 싶지 않아요
go
가다
Quickly
빠르게
let's go
갑시다
sorry
죄송합니다
he left again
그 사람 또 떠났어
Tianjin target has restored expressway
천진 목표는 고속도로를 복원했습니다
I'm going to the parking lot
주차장으로 가는데
come and see the situation
와서 상황을 봐
proceed as originally planned
원래 계획대로 진행
to the payment terminal to help prevent this
이를 방지하기 위해 결제 단말기에
OK
좋아요
you
너
The target is approaching
목표가 가까워지고 있다
Be prepared to be stopped
멈출 준비를 하세요.
Get ready to park quickly
빨리 주차 준비하세요
stop
멈추다
Where is Xiao Yi?
샤오이는 어디에 있나요?
Call an ambulance quickly
빨리 구급차를 불러주세요
And going up the mountain
그리고 산에 올라가서
can't escape
탈출할 수 없어
if you were me
당신이 나라면
I will choose the nearby mountain road
나는 가까운 산길을 선택하겠다
we are missing
우리는 실종됐다
Escape implementation tools
탈출 구현 도구
Search along the mountain road
산길을 따라 수색하다
OK
좋아요
look at her 2
그 사람 좀 봐 2
[About half an hour later]
[약 30분 후]
Is there a missing car from the police station?
경찰서에 사라진 차가 있나요?
Or a stolen car
아니면 도난당한 자동차
I found it
찾았어요
Someone pulled a motorcycle
누군가 오토바이를 끌고 갔어요
The victim called the police
피해자가 경찰에 전화함
The license plate number is ZC02J
번호판 번호는 ZC02J입니다.
There's not much gas in the car
차에 휘발유가 별로 없어요
The car owner is cheering and ready to go
차 주인이 환호하며 출발 준비를 하고 있습니다
Can't escape
탈출할 수 없어
Follow that car immediately
즉시 그 차를 따라가세요
There are also gas stations nearby
근처에 주유소도 있어요
Verified
확인됨
There is a gas station 300 meters away
300미터 거리에 주유소가 있습니다
direct
직접
92 plus 20
92 더하기 20
i just left
나 방금 나갔어
Look at the surveillance cameras
감시 카메라를 봐
This black car is carrying him
이 검은 차가 그를 태우고 있어요
There aren't many security cameras here
이곳에는 보안 카메라가 많지 않습니다.
It's impossible to catch up with him
그 사람을 따라잡는 건 불가능해
Did I annoy you?
내가 당신을 짜증나게 했나요?
No
아니요
Tianhai is not safe
텐하이는 안전하지 않아요
I can't go back
돌아갈 수 없어
I wore a ring
반지를 끼고 다녔어요
May he bless us beyond this stage
이 단계를 넘어 우리를 축복해 주시기를 바랍니다
Next
다음
The bosses asked me to give you a ride
사장님이 태워달라고 하더라구요
when
언제
as soon as possible
최대한 빨리
you have to go
너는 가야 해
This mission is a huge loss
이 임무는 엄청난 손실이다
Someone has to be responsible
누군가는 책임을 져야지
that's why i
그래서 내가
sorry
죄송합니다
I think you are
내 생각엔 당신이
Goodbye me
안녕히 계세요
We can only live as one person
우리는 오직 한 사람으로만 살아갈 수 있어요
I don't want to die in your hands
난 네 손에 죽고 싶지 않아
After getting off the car
차에서 내린 후
We will no longer be partners
우리는 더 이상 파트너가 아닙니다
I'm waiting
나는 기다리고있다
retain memory
기억을 유지하다
maybe in the future
아마 미래에는
we will never meet again
우리는 다시는 만나지 않을 것이다
Wow that
와 그거
if
만약에
Are you OK?
괜찮으세요?
Did you find the evidence?
증거는 찾았나요?
a bit strange
조금 이상하다
The place was cleaned up
장소가 깨끗해졌습니다
no useful evidence
유용한 증거가 없습니다
Even the trash can
쓰레기통이라도
Clean
깨끗한
But two days later
그런데 이틀 뒤
We will search carefully
꼼꼼히 검색해보겠습니다
I will notify you as soon as there is news
새로운 소식이 있으면 바로 알려드리겠습니다
where is the computer
컴퓨터는 어디에 있나요?
Have you checked?
확인해 보셨나요?
Computer Hard Drive Fan Page
컴퓨터 하드 드라이브 팬 페이지
zero is written
0이 쓰여있다
All records
모든 기록
has been completely deleted
완전히 삭제되었습니다
Unable to recover
복구할 수 없습니다.
so i was thinking
그래서 내가 생각하고 있었어
Xiao Yi has already noticed
Xiao Yi는 이미 알아차렸습니다.
He was prepared to retreat in advance
그는 미리 후퇴할 준비가 되어 있었다
If he has a sense of danger
그 사람이 위험감을 느낀다면
When he brought Chu Yan back to the city
그가 Chu Yan을 도시로 다시 데려왔을 때
This must be the case
이런 일이 있어야합니다
Who helped him escape?
그가 탈출하도록 도와준 사람은 누구였나요?
He's here to clean up the crime scene
그는 범죄 현장을 청소하러 왔습니다
it's out of the question
그건 말도 안 돼
This has always been Xiao Yi's residence
이곳은 항상 Xiao Yi의 거주지였습니다.
look at us
우리를 봐
And during this period
그리고 이 기간 동안
nobody
아무도
he entered their house
그는 그들의 집에 들어갔다
unless
~하지 않는 한
another door
또 다른 문
Do you have?
당신은 있나요?
impossible
불가능한
accomplish
성취하다
go check it out
가서 확인해 보세요
Who lives in this house?
이 집에는 누가 살고 있나요?
OK
좋아요
This person is about 170cm tall
이 사람 키가 170cm 정도인데
medium build
중간 빌드
Shoes 37
신발 37
This is the photo from the camera
이건 카메라로 찍은 사진
in the bar
바에서
Her height is very similar
키가 엄청 비슷하네요
Who lives here?
여기에는 누가 살고 있나요?
It should be Mr. Zhang
장 씨가 되어야 합니다.
Pretend to be a neighbor
이웃인 척
In fact he is a partner
사실 그 사람은 파트너야.
Wow that
와 그거
did you find it?
그거 찾았 어?
I asked the nearby security guard
근처 경비원에게 물어보니
Only someone who lives here can confirm
여기 사시는 분만 확인 가능해요
She is a woman in her thirties
30대 여성입니다
Her name is Zhang Ruyun
이름이 장루윤인 사람
Is he the master?
그 사람이 주인이에요?
No
아니요
The original owner is a foreigner
원래 주인은 외국인이에요
Can't contact him now
지금은 그 사람에게 연락할 수 없어요
Have you checked any nearby security cameras?
근처에 보안 카메라가 있는지 확인해 보셨나요?
Is there any live video?
라이브 영상은 없나요?
security system
보안 시스템
he was cheated
그는 속았어
Monitor information within a week
일주일 이내에 정보를 모니터링하세요.
deleted
삭제됨
what happened
무슨 일이에요
He said
그는 말했다
maybe it's a woman
어쩌면 여자일지도 몰라
Are you OK?
괜찮으세요?
I am fine
괜찮아요
I'll get you another bag
가방 하나 더 사줄게
Thanks
감사해요
No need, no need
필요없어, 필요없어
take it
가져
thank you for your welcome
환대해주셔서 감사합니다
Thanks
감사해요
Mr. Zhang
장 씨
very cautious
매우 조심스럽다
He is a difficult opponent
그는 어려운 상대이다
thank you all
다들 감사 해요
There is also an examination group
심사그룹도 있어요
Check out these two rooms
이 두 개의 방을 확인해보세요
Check it carefully
주의 깊게 확인하세요
There must be an air leak
공기 누출이 있어야 합니다.
Other effects
기타 효과
we will do our best
우리는 최선을 다할 것이다
yaw yaw
요 요
it's time
때가됐다
Huang Ziqing
황지칭
He has contact with Gao Tianyang.
그는 Gao Tianyang과 접촉하고 있습니다.
He found
그는 찾았다
fellow spy
동료 스파이
He told Gao Tianyang
그는 Gao Tianyang에게 말했습니다.
That's it
그게 다야
like i said
내가 말했듯이
I'm still not sure
아직 잘 모르겠어
He works for the national security
그는 국가안보를 위해 일한다
Or does he want to plead guilty?
아니면 유죄를 인정하고 싶은 걸까요?
Who are you
누구세요
She deliberately hid it from him
그녀는 의도적으로 그에게 숨겼습니다.
he took advantage of me
그 사람은 나를 이용했어요
Why should I avoid him?
내가 왜 그를 피해야 합니까?
This is good
이것은 좋다
Today we will ask him face to face
오늘 우리는 그에게 직접 물어볼 것입니다
Who works?
일하는 사람?
Why do we meet here?
우리가 여기서 왜 만나요?
you want to travel
당신은 여행하고 싶어
OK
좋아요
let's go
갑시다
where are we going?
우리 어디로 가는 거야?
You'll know when we arrive
우리가 도착하면 알게 될 거야
Thanks
감사해요
A lot of dishes
많은 요리
very beautiful
매우 아름다운
People who grew up by the sea
바다에서 자란 사람들
He's not bored yet
그 사람은 아직 지루하지 않아요
scene itself
장면 자체
But people are different
하지만 사람은 다르다
Of course his mood is different
물론 기분은 다르지만
Lots of sweet words
달콤한 말을 많이 하세요
i will believe
나는 믿을 것이다
since the first time
처음부터
I met you at the bar
바에서 만났어
I know
알아요
i will definitely love you
나는 반드시 당신을 사랑할 것입니다
But love at first sight is not reliable
하지만 첫눈에 반한 사랑은 믿을 수 없지
Aren't you honest enough?
당신은 충분히 정직하지 않습니까?
Huang Ziqing grew up
황자칭(Huang Ziqing)이 자랐다
Do you like lying?
당신은 거짓말을 좋아합니까?
What do you mean?
무슨 뜻이에요?
Cover up the night fog with false information
거짓정보로 밤안개를 덮어라
Looks familiar
익숙한 것 같아
when you lie
당신이 거짓말을 할 때
don't close your eyes
눈을 감지 마세요
really cool
정말 멋진
do not you?
그렇지 않습니까?
I can live in the night fog
나는 밤안개 속에서도 살 수 있다
In the night fog
밤안개 속에서
thank you for your cooperation
도와 주셔서 감사합니다
this is correct
이게 맞다
we come from the same road
우리는 같은 길에서 왔어
but different
하지만 다르다
I gave you the basic card
기본카드를 주셨는데
until one day
언젠가까지
You want to destroy this alliance
당신은 이 동맹을 파괴하고 싶어합니다
you can kill me anytime
넌 언제든지 날 죽일 ​​수 있어
I can't even fight
난 싸울 수도 없어
Really?
정말?
Did you give it to me?
나한테 준 거야?
for me?
나를 위한?
I really thought
나는 정말로 생각했다
See you sincerely
진심으로 만나요
Who knew we were deceiving each other?
우리가 서로 속이고 있다는 걸 누가 알았겠어요?
say what you want to say
당신이 말하고 싶은 것을 말하세요
between us
우리 사이
No need to speak
말할 필요도 없어
Why did you lie to me?
왜 나 한테 거짓말 했어?
anything?
아무것?
"Gao Tianyang" means "Gu'an"
"Gao Tianyang"은 "Gu'an"을 의미합니다.
if you don't speak
당신이 말을하지 않으면
This means you agree to this
이는 귀하가 이에 동의한다는 의미입니다.
Yes or no
예 혹은 아니오
No
아니요
I won't tell you
나는 당신에게 말하지 않을 것이다
Because they have a system
시스템을 갖고 있기 때문에
unable to express
표현할 수 없다
your identity
당신의 정체성
And you?
당신은요?
What is your identity?
당신의 정체성은 무엇입니까?
Do you think
당신은 생각합니까?
Are you going crazy?
미칠 것 같아?
How should we deal with this problem?
우리는 이 문제를 어떻게 처리해야 합니까?
It's a pity you don't know
모르시다니 아쉽네요
How much do I know?
나는 얼마나 알고 있나요?
I'm not Guo An
나는 궈안이 아니다
if i don't reach the truth
내가 진실에 도달하지 못한다면
I won't come to see you
난 당신을 만나러 오지 않을 거예요
I hope so
나는 희망한다
explanation to me
나에게 설명
Who gave you permission to investigate me?
누가 당신에게 나를 조사하도록 허락했습니까?
Does it matter?
그게 그렇게 중요한 건가?
Yes
예
I should know where you stand
당신이 어디에 서 있는지 알아야겠어요
Who are you
누구세요
Or are you a spy?
아니면 스파이인가요?
to investigate me
나를 조사하기 위해
as a friend
친구로
as an ally
동맹국으로서
For you
당신을 위한
if you really
만약 당신이 정말로
Verify your true identity
실제 신원을 확인하세요
You don't need to be so sneaky
너무 뻔뻔할 필요는 없어
but if you
하지만 만약 당신이
as a spy
스파이로서
I am disappointed
나는 실망했다
Still trying to deal with the night fog
아직도 밤안개를 처리하려고 애쓰고 있어요
correct
옳은
Yewu asked me to go see you
유우가 나한테 보러 가자고 했어
but i am
하지만 나는
I want to know the truth
나는 진실을 알고 싶다
Huang Ziqing
황지칭
Did you lie to me?
나한테 거짓말했어요?
Are you lying to me?
나한테 거짓말하는 거야?
since we met
우리가 만난 이후로
so we play games
그래서 우리는 게임을 해요
until we go out
우리가 나갈 때까지
all of these
이들 모두
in your plan
당신의 계획에
you always lie to me
당신은 항상 나에게 거짓말을
You're always using me, aren't you?
당신은 항상 나를 이용하고 있는 거죠, 그렇죠?
I didn't take advantage of you
나는 당신을 이용하지 않았다
i am saving you
내가 당신을 구하고 있어요
you still lie to me
당신은 아직도 나에게 거짓말을 하고 있어요
Even now you're lying to me
지금도 넌 나에게 거짓말을 하고 있어
Huang Ziqing
황지칭
I just want to ask you
나는 단지 당신에게 묻고 싶습니다.
Is it your heart?
당신의 마음인가요?
Don't you feel guilty about me?
당신은 나에 대해 죄책감을 느끼지 않습니까?
Yes or no?
예 혹은 아니오?
i thought i hurt you
난 내가 당신에게 상처를 입혔다고 생각했어요
I really thought
나는 정말로 생각했다
When I was in Macau
마카오에 있었을 때
I was in Macau
나는 마카오에 있었다
So I didn't think anything
그래서 아무 생각도 안 했는데
I will come back to save you
나는 당신을 구하러 다시 올 것이다
But now it seems
그런데 지금은 그런 것 같다
you are lying to me
당신은 나에게 거짓말을하고 있습니다
at first
처음에는
this is me
이게 나야
I am silly Huang Ziqing
나는 바보 황자칭
You're the stupidest thing I've ever done
넌 내가 한 일 중 가장 멍청한 짓이야
Are you still helping Ye Wu?
아직도 예우를 돕고 있나요?
if you continue like this
계속 이대로라면
no one can save you
아무도 당신을 구할 수 없습니다
I don't want you to save me
나는 당신이 나를 구하는 것을 원하지 않습니다
I can go out
나갈 수 있어요
I'm back for you
나는 당신을 위해 돌아왔다
Lorak
로락
I am free
나는 자유 다
Huang Ziqing, do you know?
황자칭, 아시나요?
And you
당신은요
at any time
언제든지
Let Gao Tianyang catch me.
Gao Tianyang이 나를 잡게 해주세요.
Yes or no?
예 혹은 아니오?
Yes or no
예 혹은 아니오
say
말하다
Say something, answer me
뭐라고 말해봐 대답해줘
sorry
죄송합니다
Do you really think so?
정말 그렇게 생각해?
Say I don't know anything?
내가 아무것도 모른다고?
you are listening to me
당신은 내 말을 듣고 있어요
You act with me all the time
넌 항상 나와 함께 행동해
And your acting skills are very good
그리고 연기력도 너무 좋고
You almost lied to me
당신은 나에게 거의 거짓말을 했어요
but do you think
하지만 당신은 생각합니까?
that love
그 사랑
you can perform
당신은 수행할 수 있습니다
I hope
나는 희망
face me honestly
솔직하게 나를 만나다
Give me an explanation
설명 좀 해주세요
OK
좋아요
After I came back from Macau
마카오에서 돌아온 후
my identity
내 정체성
Discovered by his brother
동생이 발견한
He cares about our feelings
그분은 우리의 감정에 관심을 갖고 계십니다
He didn't tell about this
그는 이것에 대해 말하지 않았습니다
To national security
국가 안보에
but he asked me
그런데 그 사람이 나한테 물었어
Not working for spies
스파이를 위해 일하지 않음
He asked me to provide him with evidence
나한테 증거를 보여달라고 하더군요
To help solve the case
사건 해결을 돕기 위해
make an achievement
성과를 내다
This is a fact
이건 사실이다
Why are you avoiding me?
왜 나를 피하는 거죠?
this matter
이 문제
A third party cannot know
제3자는 알 수 없습니다.
but I do not have
하지만 난 없어
i'm using you
나는 당신을 사용하고 있습니다
i always want to
난 항상 그러고 싶어
Be your scapegoat
당신의 희생양이 되세요
take you to the beach
널 해변으로 데려가줘
Night fog helps
밤 안개가 도움이 된다
no future
미래가 없다
What's wrong with you?
왜 그래?
What have you achieved?
당신은 무엇을 달성했나요?
you are always at the beach
당신은 항상 해변에 있어요
real dangerous man
진짜 위험한 남자
this is me
이게 나야
if you are in danger
당신이 위험에 처해 있다면
he won't leave you
그 사람은 널 떠나지 않을 거야
Ignore you
당신을 무시
but we are all different
하지만 우리는 모두 다릅니다
They are taking advantage of my family's safety.
그들은 우리 가족의 안전을 이용하고 있습니다.
come threaten me
와서 나를 위협해
i must promise
약속해야겠어
their safety
그들의 안전
so
그래서
I have no chance to go ashore
해변에 갈 기회가 없어요
So I'm the only one who can save you
그러니 너를 구할 수 있는 사람은 나뿐이야
I'm here to tell you today
오늘은 너에게 말하려고 왔어
I found a spy
스파이를 찾았어요
He is also a gamer
그 사람도 게이머인데
Discover that special game
그 특별한 게임을 발견해보세요
When he found out everything was a scam
모든 것이 사기였다는 걸 알았을 때
Might ruin the dream
꿈을 망칠 수도 있어
virtual life is over
가상생활은 끝났다
reality must be punished
현실은 처벌받아야 한다
So that's it now
그럼 이제 됐어
He went to surrender
그는 항복하러 갔다
for him
그를 위해
This is the best result
이것이 최고의 결과입니다
Ways I can save myself
나 자신을 구할 수 있는 방법
He was an informant for Gao Tianyang
그는 Gao Tianyang의 정보원이었습니다.
you are my partner
당신은 내 파트너입니다
always
언제나
I won't give it to you
나는 그것을 당신에게주지 않을 것입니다
you must tell me
당신은 나에게 말해야합니다
tell me these things
이것저것 말해봐
Sadness is shown really well.
슬픔이 정말 잘 표현되어 있어요.
I'm touched by both of you
두 분 모두 감동받았어요
we will meet again
우리는 다시 만날 것입니다
You set a trap for me
당신은 나를 위해 함정을 설정했습니다
sorry
죄송합니다
For a betrayal like yours
당신 같은 배신을 위해
Don't use any more tricks
더 이상 트릭을 사용하지 마십시오
how can we
우리는 어떻게 할 수 있습니까?
to know the truth
진실을 알기 위해
i can't do anything
난 아무것도 할 수 없어
you are fighting
당신은 싸우고 있습니다
you have to take me here
나를 여기로 데려가야 해
I can't offend you
나는 당신을 화나게 할 수 없습니다
I can't offend Gao Tianyang.
나는 Gao Tianyang을 화나게 할 수 없습니다.
I have no idea
나는 전혀 모른다
Will he come to your rescue?
그가 당신을 구하러 올까요?
you
너
If you dare to look for it
감히 찾아보신다면
i think you are brave
내 생각엔 당신이 용감한 것 같아요
But I guess you don't dare
하지만 넌 감히 그럴 수 없을 것 같아
you are just a bully
넌 그냥 깡패야
we are gamers
우리는 게이머다
don't motivate me
나에게 동기를 부여하지 마세요
I won't embarrass you
난 당신을 당황하게 하지 않을 거예요
Don't embarrass me, okay?
날 당황하게 하지 마, 알았지?
I gotta go
난 가야 해
Didn't you say that?
그렇게 말하지 않았나요?
don't embarrass me
나를 당황하게 하지 마세요
As long as you cooperate with us
당신이 우리와 협력하는 한
I will treat you well
내가 잘 대해줄게
How can I work with you?
어떻게 당신과 함께 일할 수 있나요?
What did you say to the NSA?
NSA에 뭐라고 말했어요?
national security office
국가안보실
I don't know who the National Security Agency is
국가안전보위부가 누구인지는 모르지만
I am Gao Tianyang's informant.
저는 Gao Tianyang의 제보자입니다.
he is my brother
그는 내 동생입니다
Do you know how to help me?
나를 돕는 방법을 알고 있나요?
how can i help you
어떻게 도와 드릴까요
I told him
나는 그에게 말했다
The task you gave me
당신이 나에게 준 임무
Your last fetched data
마지막으로 가져온 데이터
He is the one who asked you to revise
수정해달라고 요청하신 분입니다
Yes
예
you are honest
당신은 정직하다
I feel uncomfortable
불편하다
What should I tell you?
내가 당신에게 무엇을 말해야합니까?
He forced me to say
그는 나에게 이렇게 말하라고 강요했다.
but you don't believe me
하지만 당신은 나를 믿지 않습니다
Are you cheap?
당신은 싸다?
you deceived us
당신은 우리를 속였습니다
you are very frank
당신은 매우 솔직해요
what can I do?
어떡해?
you must be punished
당신은 처벌을 받아야합니다
What punishment?
무슨 처벌이요?
hope you can figure it out
당신이 그것을 알아낼 수 있기를 바랍니다
It's impossible to come back alive
살아서 돌아오는 건 불가능해